Lorenzo, you you ran the the 4-2 and it
was reported that you weren't fully
healthy when you did that. What do you
What do you actually run?
I probably could have ran a little bit
faster, but that's what That's what I
have for that day. So, I probably don't
know. Maybe a little bit faster. Do
humans run faster than 4-2 or like
Where's
>> Whatever that I want? Can people
actually run faster than 4-2 or do like
what are we talking about here? Like
what what's
>> No, I probably could have ran a low 4-2.
The thing that got me was the jump just
cuz I had to jump with my left arm
instead of my right. So, that was a
little bit different. So, I feel like I
could have jumped a higher there for
sure, but I don't know, man.
How is your shoulder now and what's kind
of the rehab process like for you? Yeah,
I have a great team at Ohio State that's
going to take care of me in this whole
draft process. Shout out Adam Stewart.
And then Ryan Rock was my surgeon. So,
on track. I'm excited to be I'm going to
be ready to go.
There's a lot of different timelines
that are kind of floating around. What's
the timeline that you're expecting right
now that you're working with? I'm going
to go in. Still be working with the
team. It's going to be really really up
to them. I'll be ready for when it's
time for camp when it's time to compete.
When jobs and stuff are on the line and
I got to show it's time to really play.
That's when I'll be ready to go. So,
you're expecting
your expectation is to be ready for
training camp? Is that what you said?
Yes, sir.
How did you accept the news that you
were going from wide receiver to safety?
I mean, was that something good? And how
did that help you as a safety?
Yes, sir. I feel like being able to
understand route concepts I used to run
those route concepts. How I wanted to
attack a defense. How I wanted to attack
DBs. So, I feel like my overall my my
football acumen has just increased
especially working here with you know,
defensive side of ball with Matt
Patricia, Tim Walton, Matt Guerrieri.
This Ohio State staff feel like it's
prepared me well for the NFL and really
the position switch as well. Just all
those tools about to come together here
at the safety position, nickel position,
really whatever Whatever the team needs
me to do. Special teams even as well.
Are you aware of the Ohio State to New
Orleans pipeline that has existed for
some time and what you're carrying on
here?
I'm really not too familiar with all the
Ohio State I know my boy Chris Olave is
there. Great player, but overall I'm I'm
excited to keep that pipeline going
though for sure.
And how much time have you spent in New
Orleans if at all?
I haven't been. I haven't been. So, I'm
excited to get down there go down to the
south. Really only been in the Midwest
my whole life. So, excited for the
change of scenery, new people, new
environment.
Was there a player you modeled your
style after as a kid?
I wouldn't say so. I'm definitely going
to try to play like me. I feel like I'm
in a unique situation just with my skill
set and different things like that.
There's a lot of players in the NFL I
like. Some of them are ball hawking guys
like Xavier McKinney. Guys who can move
around like Trevon Diggs,
Shamari Conner. Different guys like
that, but I'm really focused on my own
play style. Being able to have range. Be
able to go down and cover three. Special
teams. Be able to get the ball in my
hands and be effective in that way. So,
feel like my play style it's it's me.
Lorenzo Styles.
Lorenzo, did How come you didn't return
more kicks and is that something teams
have talked to you about doing? Yeah.
See, at Ohio State they had this thing
where they like put receivers back
there, offensive guys. So, I was Coach
Day let me get a chance especially cuz
let me get a chance the first time that
I got back there. I was like probably
five like way too deep. Wasn't supposed
to take it out. And I knew if I touched
the ball I was taking it to the end
zone. So, I'm excited I'm really excited
about the NFL and how how important that
is in field position especially in the
NFL game now. That was like the first
Ohio State kick return touchdown in like
15 years or something like that. Is that
right? Yeah, that's correct. How did it
feel to be a part of that history?
It felt great.
Our special teams we were really trying
to work on that part of our game and
keep continuing to improve. So, being
able to impact the game and then the my
teammates did a great job. And then the
coach Nate Ebner who played in the NFL
especially played for a long time. It
was great to
be able to have that success alongside
him.
Lorenzo, what was it like, you know,
growing up in your house with your
brother and how much influence your dad
have on you?
He started that football that football
fire that's still within us within my
brother within me. We're competitive. It
wasn't necessarily about
like he didn't really talk about his his
career necessarily, but he instilled all
the things about what it's like to be a
pro that we now recognize as we're
older.
Were you hoping to be drafted with your
brother or you glad you you get to go
elsewhere? How are you kind of feeling
about going into this? Yeah, I'm ready
to start my my own legacy. We all both
we have the Styles family. He has his.
He has I have mine. So, I'm excited to
be in a a situation where as a player
it's a
him that's a compete against each other.
I'll be on opposite ends hopefully down
the line. Maybe he can come to the
Saints and we'll be able to to ball out
together down the line.
Lorenzo, how familiar are you with the
way that Brandon Staley utilizes sort of
the star slot role and and and is that a
position you feel that you could see
yourself in?
Yes, sir. Me and Coach Patricia so we
were doing some just watching different
games. So, I watched Coach a lot and
yeah, I feel like I'm going to be like
being able to be versatile in the
defense. Being able to run different
two-high structures. Play the deep half.
Play the post when we get when we rotate
to three.
I'm excited. I got I got a lot to learn.
But I'm I'm excited. How do you feel
about potentially rushing the passer?
I mean, you can see the 4-2 straight up
there. Have a good disguise. They won't
be able to see me coming. So, I feel
like it's going to be another element to
help the defense out.
Lorenzo, you graduated with your father
it says here. What was that day like for
you?
It meant a lot. So, my dad went back.
He's actually said to coach in college
football you have to have your degree.
That's something he wanted to do for a
long time. So, being able to see him and
it was funny he took school so serious.
He was a dude high GPA, all A's type of
guy. But being able to graduate with
him, being able to see him coaching.
He's coaching at Bowling Green now along
his former teammate Eddie George.
It's a how far the whole Styles family
has came and everyone's chasing their
dreams. So, it's it's great for all of
everything we've been praying and
manifesting come to fruition.
Coming from a football family the way
that you do, how would you describe your
work ethic away from the football field?
I love football. It's really it's my
life. I'm a professional. I feel like
I'm I'm excited to spend 13-14 hours in
the facility. I'm excited to keep
getting better every single year.
I love attacking the game. Uh
Yeah, I love it. There's nothing else
nothing else I want to be doing.
Anything else?
Thank you, guys.
>> Awesome. Thank you very much.